Hello guys! Will we be on time
for the launch of our new insurance product?
Well, the validation of the product notice
takes more time than expected...
How come?
The blueprint was provided 3 months ago!
Yes but many actors must align on the content.
The business stakeholders,
the partnership,  legal, ...
... actuarial, marketing,
communication departments...
And this is just for Cardif side
...but you have the same
on the Business Partner side on the commercial aspects...
I confirm: each single word, image or chapter
has to be reviewed...
and it implies many exchanges, discussions, comings and goings...
So, what is the latest version
of the working document?
You mean the one from the Cardif legal department
or from the Partner marketing?
They are not on the same version ?!?
I'm not sure they are dealing
with the very last one
Let me check my emails, Jiras & Teams,
with other scrum masters and product managers...
A suivre... /
To be continued...